Contact

behdad.k7@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/behdad-karimi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Business Analysis
Project Management

Languages

Persian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Full Professional)
Arabic (Elementary)

Certifications

What is Data Science? By IBM Data Science Math Skills by Duke University

Fundamentals of Visualization with Tableau

Visual Analytics with Tableau Machine Learning with Python

Publications

Location Recommendation based on location-based social networks for Entertainment services

Effect of Cloud Computing Systems in Terms of Service Quality of Knowledge Management Systems

Behdad Karimi

Data Science enthusiast

Summary

I'm interested in data science. I studied software engineering and got my master's degree in information technology. For a while, I worked as a business consultant and did business planning (BP and BDP). As a co-founder, I was involved in two startups and had technical responsibility for these two startups. I have been following Data Science and AI topics since I was a student and had two articles and several activities during my time at the university. I've been seriously into Data Science for a while now, working as a freelancer and learning at the same time.

Skilled in Java, Python, Databases, Tableau, and English. Strong information technology professional with a Master's degree focused in Information Technology from Qom University.

Experience

iNkarnet | اینکارنت Co-founder and CTO February 2017 - April 2019 (2 years 3 months)

Handica | اندى Co-Founder and CTO June 2017 - June 2018 (1 year 1 month) Fars Province, Iran

Education

Qom University

Master's degree, Information Technology (2013 - 2015)

Fasa University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering · (2007 - 2011)